(Raj:)but she was so cute I panicked
and said,
"Wouldn't it be easier
if instead of talking
(Raj:)we could just sniff
each other's butts?"
(Bernadette:)Well, Stuart's cute in his own way.
(Stuart:)When I was a baby, my mother
called me her little possum.
(Raj:)-Are possums cute?
-Not at all.
(Howard:)If you're so intimidated
by talking to attractive girls,
(Howard:)maybe you should practice
by talking to regular people.
(Raj:)You mean like fatties and uggos?
(Bernadette:)Or maybe just stop talking.
(Howard:)I'm serious. Go to the mall,
talk to anybody, practice.
(Howard:)That way, when you eventually
do talk to a cute girl,
(Howard:)-it won't be so scary.
-Or just keep dating the possum.
(Voice on television:)Parsa doesn't have
those kind of resources.
No, and that is why he had
Erin Pace rewire it...
(Leonard:)I'm so proud of you.
(Penny:)We haven't even
gotten to my scene yet.
(Leonard:)I know, but you're going to be a TV
star and you haven't left me yet.
(Leonard:)That takes guts.